<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<template>
    <project-name>Queen's Arc</project-name>
    <standard-project-info>
        <key>
            <town>Queenstown</town>
            <tooltip/>
            <uri/>
        </key>
        <key>
            <point>868|1280</point>
        </key>
        <key>
            <latitude>1.2898083</latitude>
            <longitude>103.8011026</longitude>
        </key>
        <key>
            <completion-date>3Q2027</completion-date>
            <tooltip>
                				
                
					This is an estimated date that the flat will be completed and ready for key collection, and the actual completion date will depend on the progress of construction works on site. As the Estimated Completion Date (ECD) is indicative only, HDB shall not be responsible for any damage or loss arising from a change in the ECD.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>
					After booking the flat, buyers may check for updates via My HDBPage on HDB InfoWEB, as the construction of the project progresses.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>
					Note: The contractual date in the Agreement for Lease by which HDB is required to deliver vacant possession of the booked flat to buyers is known as the Delivery Possession Date (DPD), which is 18 months after the ECD. Currently, the estimated DPD is 31 March 2029.
                			
            </tooltip>
            <uri/>
        </key>
        <key>
            <remaining-lease>99</remaining-lease>
            <tooltip>The 3- and 4-room flats are sold on a 99-year lease.</tooltip>
            <uri/>
        </key>
        <key>
            <selection-month>October 2021 to June 2022</selection-month>
        </key>
        <key>
            <est-waiting-time>67 months</est-waiting-time>
        </key>
        <key>
            <lease-period-2rm/>
        </key>
        <key>
            <price-tooltip>
                				
                
					The indicative price range of the flats exclude grants, and are based on 99-year leases.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>
					Actual prices may vary based on the actual attributes of the flats at the time of selection. Find out details of the Optional Component Scheme offered for this project.
                			
            </price-tooltip>
        </key>
        <unit-details>
            <ukey>
                <flat-type>3-Room (Income Ceiling $14,000)</flat-type>
                <supply>76</supply>
                <est-floor-area-lower>69</est-floor-area-lower>
                <est-floor-area-upper>69</est-floor-area-upper>
                <tooltip>Refers to the estimated area of the whole apartment, comprising the internal floor area and the air-conditioner ledge.</tooltip>
                <est-internal-floor-area-lower>66</est-internal-floor-area-lower>
                <est-internal-floor-area-upper>66</est-internal-floor-area-upper>
                <tooltip>Refers to the estimated area of the apartment computed based on the centre line of the apartment wall.</tooltip>
                <price-range-lower>382000</price-range-lower>
                <price-range-upper>464000</price-range-upper>
                <finishes-and-fittings-text>
                    <non-optional>
                        						
                        
   						&lt;h4>Finishes and Fittings&lt;/h4>
						&lt;br>
						&lt;h5>Non-Optional Finishes&lt;/h5>
						&lt;br>
						&lt;p>
						More than just a well-designed and functional interior, the 3-room flats will come with the following finishes and fittings: 
	  					&lt;/p>						
						&lt;ul>
							&lt;li>Floor tiles in the:&lt;/li>
	    					&lt;ul>
								&lt;li>Bathrooms&lt;/li>
								&lt;li>Household shelter&lt;/li>
	        					&lt;li>Kitchen/ utility&lt;/li>
							
	    					&lt;/ul>
							&lt;li>Wall tiles in the: &lt;/li>
	    					&lt;ul>
	        					&lt;li>Bathrooms&lt;/li>
	   						&lt;li>Kitchen/ utility&lt;/li>
	    					&lt;/ul>
	    				&lt;/ul>
						
                        					
                    </non-optional>
                    <optional>
                        <floor>
                            <header>Flooring for Living/ Dining, Dry Kitchen, and Bedrooms </header>
                            <price>3340</price>
                            <text>
                                							
                                
							&lt;ul>
	    					&lt;li>Vinyl strip flooring in the bedrooms&lt;/li>
							&lt;li>Polished porcelain floor tiles in the living/ dining, dry kitchen&lt;/li> 
							&lt;/ul>
							
                                							
                            </text>
                        </floor>
                        <door>
                            <header>Internal Doors and Sanitary Fittings</header>
                            <price>2700</price>
                            <text>
                                							
                                
							&lt;ul>
							&lt;ul>
	    					&lt;li>2 laminated UPVC bedroom doors&lt;/li>
							&lt;li>2 laminated UPVC folding bathroom doors&lt;/li>
	   						&lt;li>Wash basin with tap mixer&lt;/li>
							&lt;li>Shower set with bath/ shower mixer&lt;/li>
							&lt;/ul>
							
                                							
                            </text>
                        </door>
                    </optional>
                </finishes-and-fittings-text>
            </ukey>
            <ukey>
                <flat-type>4-Room</flat-type>
                <supply>534</supply>
                <est-floor-area-lower>93</est-floor-area-lower>
                <est-floor-area-upper>93</est-floor-area-upper>
                <tooltip>Refers to the estimated area of the whole apartment, comprising the internal floor area and the air-conditioner ledge.</tooltip>
                <est-internal-floor-area-lower>90</est-internal-floor-area-lower>
                <est-internal-floor-area-upper>90</est-internal-floor-area-upper>
                <tooltip>Refers to the estimated area of the apartment computed based on the centre line of the apartment wall.</tooltip>
                <price-range-lower>540000</price-range-lower>
                <price-range-upper>670000</price-range-upper>
                <finishes-and-fittings-text>
                    <non-optional>
                        						
                        
   						&lt;h4>Finishes and Fittings&lt;/h4>
						&lt;br>
						&lt;h5>Non-Optional Finishes&lt;/h5>
						&lt;br>
						&lt;p>
						More than just a well-designed and functional interior, the 4-room flats will come with the following finishes and fittings:   
	  					&lt;/p>						
						&lt;ul>
							&lt;li>Floor tiles in the:&lt;/li>
	    					&lt;ul>
								&lt;li>Bathrooms&lt;/li>
								&lt;li>Household shelter&lt;/li>
	        					&lt;li>Kitchen&lt;/li>
							&lt;li>Service yard&lt;/li>
							
	    					&lt;/ul>
							&lt;li>Wall tiles in the: &lt;/li>
	    					&lt;ul>
	        					&lt;li>Bathrooms&lt;/li>
    							&lt;li>Kitchen&lt;/li>
	    					&lt;/ul>
	    				&lt;/ul>
						
                        					
                    </non-optional>
                    <optional>
                        <floor>
                            <header>Flooring for Living/ Dining and Bedrooms </header>
                            <price>4970</price>
                            <text>
                                							
                                
							&lt;ul>
	    					&lt;li>Vinyl strip flooring in the bedrooms&lt;/li>
							&lt;li>Polished porcelain floor tiles in the living/ dining&lt;/li> 
							&lt;/ul>
							
                                							
                            </text>
                        </floor>
                        <door>
                            <header>Internal Doors and Sanitary Fittings</header>
                            <price>3080</price>
                            <text>
                                							
                                
							&lt;ul>
							&lt;ul>
	    					&lt;li>3 laminated UPVC bedroom doors&lt;/li>
							&lt;li>2 laminated UPVC folding bathroom doors&lt;/li>
	   						&lt;li>Wash basin with tap mixer&lt;/li>
							&lt;li>Shower set with bath/ shower mixer&lt;/li>
							&lt;/ul>
							
                                							
                            </text>
                        </door>
                    </optional>
                </finishes-and-fittings-text>
            </ukey>
        </unit-details>
        <overview>
            <p>
                			
                
			&lt;h6>Queenstown&lt;/h6>
			&lt;br>
			Queen's Arc &lt;a class="audioBtn queens-arc">&lt;i class="fas fa-volume-up">&lt;/i>&lt;/a> is bounded by Queen's Crescent and Queensway Drive. You can choose from the 610 units of 3- and 4-room flats on offer, which will be housed in 2 residential blocks ranging from 23 to 39 storeys. Together with an additional residential block of rental flats, there will be 3 residential blocks in this development.
			&lt;br>&lt;br>
			The residential blocks at Queen's Arc will curve along a series of landscaped trails designed to promote wellness. Along these wellness trails, you will be able to find pavilions, fitness stations, and playgrounds. Complementing these trails is a heritage trail designed to bring residents through the history of Queensway.
			&lt;br>&lt;br>
			Queen's Arc will be served by a Multi-Storey Car Park, which will feature a garden on its roof, and a community hub on the ground floor. The roof garden will come with adult and elderly fitness stations and a jogging loop, while the community hub offers a variety of facilities such as a childcare centre, an eating house, a minimart, and other shops. Other facilities at Queen' Arc include roof gardens atop each of the 2 residential blocks, as well as a residents’ network centre. Please refer to the site plan for the facilities provided in this development. Facilities in this development will be accessible by the public.
			&lt;br>&lt;br>    
			
                			
            </p>
        </overview>
        <notes>
            <p>
                			
                HDB precincts are planned to serve the evolving needs of the community. There are spaces catered for future inclusion of amenities/ facilities (such as childcare centres, elderly-related facilities, education centres, residents' network centres, and day activity centres), commercial facilities (such as shops and eating houses), mechanical and electrical rooms, and such other facilities depending on the prevailing needs. These spaces could be in the void decks, common property, car parks, or stand-alone community buildings.
			&lt;br>&lt;br>
			To facilitate your flat application, we have provided information on the surrounding land use, proposed facilities and their locations in the maps and plans of individual projects. As the information provided is based on the current planning intent of the relevant authorities, such information is indicative only and subject to review from time to time.
			&lt;br>&lt;br>
			&lt;ul>
			&lt;li>Get answers to &lt;a href="https://www.hdb.gov.sg/cs/infoweb/residential/buying-a-flat/new/buying-process/application-procedure/faqs-for-sales-launch">Frequently Asked Questions on sales launches&lt;/a>&lt;/li>
			&lt;br>
   			&lt;li>Visit the virtual showflats at &lt;a href="https://www.hdb.gov.sg/mynicehomegallery?utm_source=Aug21website&amp;utm_medium=link&amp;utm_campaign=MNHG">My Nice Home Gallery&lt;/a> and get interior decor ideas&lt;/li>
			&lt;/ul>
			
                			
            </p>
        </notes>
    </standard-project-info>
    <template-body>
        <row>
            <header>Eco-Friendly Features</header>
        </row>
        <row>
            <p>
                				
                &lt;p>To encourage green and sustainable living, Queen’s Arc will have several eco-friendly features such as:&lt;/p>
				&lt;ul>
					&lt;li>Separate chutes for recyclable waste&lt;/li>
					&lt;li>Regenerative lifts to reduce energy consumption&lt;/li>
					&lt;li>Bicycle stands to encourage cycling as an environmentally-friendly form of transport&lt;/li>
					&lt;li>Parking spaces to facilitate future provision of electrical vehicle charging stations &lt;/li>
					&lt;li>Use of sustainable products in the development&lt;/li>
					&lt;li>Active, Beautiful, Clean Waters design features to clean rainwater and beautify the landscapes&lt;/li>
				&lt;/ul>
                			
            </p>
        </row>
        <row>
            <template1>
                <photo-folder>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template1</photo-folder>
                <photos>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template1/1.jpg</photo>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template1/2.jpg</photo>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template1/3.jpg</photo>
                </photos>
            </template1>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>Smart Solutions</header>
        </row>
        <row>
            <p>
                &lt;p>Queen's Arc will come with the following smart solutions to reduce energy usage, and contribute to a sustainable and safer living environment:  &lt;/p>
				&lt;ul>
					&lt;li>Smart Lighting in common areas to reduce energy usage&lt;/li>
					&lt;li>Smart Pneumatic Waste Conveyance System to optimise the deployment of resources for cleaner and fuss-free waste disposal&lt;/li>
				&lt;/ul>
            </p>
        </row>
        <row>
            <header>About Queenstown</header>
        </row>
        <row>
            <p>
                 
				
                
				Residents at Queen's Arc can shop and dine to their hearts' content, with Queensway Shopping Centre and Anchorpoint Shopping Centre located near the development, and the neighbourhood centre along Mei Ling Street located nearby. Discover more heartland shops around Queenstown by visiting  &lt;a href="https://www.hdb.gov.sg/residential/where2shop/explore/queenstown">Where2Shop@HDB&lt;/a>. Alexandra Hospital is also in the vicinity of Queen's Arc. More shopping options are available in Bukit Merah town, like IKEA, Alexandra Central, and Alexandra Village with a food centre.
				&lt;br>&lt;br>
				A host of recreational amenities are available for Queenstown residents. You can take a dip or work up a sweat at the Queenstown Swimming Complex and Stadium, or take a stroll along Alexandra-Queensway Park Connector. Enjoy a quiet moment at Queenstown Public Library, or explore new hobbies and skills at Queenstown Community Centre.
				&lt;br>&lt;br>
				Queen's Arc is a short drive from the Ayer Rajah Expressway (AYE) and is served by Queenstown MRT station. Schools in Queenstown include New Town Primary School, Queenstown Primary and Secondary School, and Queensway Secondary School.
				
                			
            </p>
        </row>
        <row>
            <template2>
                <photo-folder>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template2</photo-folder>
                <photos>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template2/1.jpg</photo>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template2/2.jpg</photo>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template2/3.jpg</photo>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template2/4.jpg</photo>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template2/5.jpg</photo>
                    <photo>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/template2/6.jpg</photo>
                </photos>
            </template2>
        </row>
    </template-body>
    <resources>
        <town-map>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/townmap/townmap_qt_n2c1.jpg</town-map>
        <carousel>
            <link>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/carousel/01_perspective.jpg</link>
            <link>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/carousel/02_perspective.jpg</link>
            <link>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/carousel/03_siteplan_qt_n2c1.jpg</link>
        </carousel>
        <sound>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/sound/qt_n2c1.mp3</sound>
        <genspecs>
            <genspecs-3rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/genspecs/genspecs_qt_n2c1_3rm_4rm.jpg</genspecs-3rm>
            <genspecs-4rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/genspecs/genspecs_qt_n2c1_3rm_4rm.jpg</genspecs-4rm>
        </genspecs>
        <layoutideas>
            <layoutideas-3rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/layoutideas/layoutideas_qt_n2c1_3rm.jpg</layoutideas-3rm>
            <layoutideas-4rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/layoutideas/layoutideas_qt_n2c1_4rm.jpg</layoutideas-4rm>
        </layoutideas>
        <resale>
            <resale-3rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/resale/resale_qt_n2c1_3rm.jpg</resale-3rm>
            <resale-4rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/resale/resale_qt_n2c1_4rm.jpg</resale-4rm>
        </resale>
        <oydh>
            <oydh-3rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/oydh/oydh_qt_n2c1_3rm.jpg</oydh-3rm>
            <oydh-4rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/oydh/oydh_qt_n2c1_4rm.jpg</oydh-4rm>
        </oydh>
        <ocsleaflet>
            <ocsleaflet-3rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/ocsleaflet/ocsleaflet_qt_n2c1_3rm_4rm(1).png</ocsleaflet-3rm>
            <ocsleaflet-4rm>2021-08/bto/qt_n2c1/ocsleaflet/ocsleaflet_qt_n2c1_3rm_4rm(1).png</ocsleaflet-4rm>
        </ocsleaflet>
        <ocs/>
    </resources>
</template>